sakuralive.com 2013-05-14

# Free Japanese Webcam: Private Policy Is Taken Very Seriously At Sakuralive.com

**Sakuralive.com** allows you to chat privately with our sexy Japanese camgirls and to enjoy their most intimate and private moments with you. We are committed to keeping your information private, and this is very important to us. All of your personal data shared with us is kept private. This includes information such as your Name, Address, and Email Address. These personal details are only used for verification purposes and not shared with anyone else. Rest assured that we have put certain security measures in place to ensure that your information is only used as promised. Should you need to update any of your personal details, you can easily contact support to have this information changed in our system once we verify your identity.

If you want to upgrade your membership to find performers who are naughty enough to do things like masturbating on camera, you just need to buy Points. There are many sexy camgirls to watch and the environment is fun. The girls can even watch you on your own webcam while you get off on watching them, so there is a lot of interaction that goes both ways. The site is fun and loaded with hours of entertainment.

Although there are free Japanese webcam sluts to check out, you only get to interact with them by joining and buying some points. 

##   
Find the **Japanese live camgirls** who are masturbating online now.

This way you can see them getting off on live webcam and sharing this intimate moment with you.

Be sure to review our commitment to privacy to understand how we use your personal information that you give to us on the site before you chat with horny Japanese sluts. You can feel safe that your information is kept secured tightly and not shared with anyone else. If you have any questions regarding this policy, you can always contact support with any specific questions that you might have.

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on SakuraLive web site. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email Address

**The Way We Use Information:**  
Customer information such as name, address and email may be verified between SakuraLive and your credit card issuing bank for security purposes. Information is not shared with any other parties. Your email may also be used to contact you.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us at [ support@sakuralive.com](mailto:support@sakuralive.com) You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
